A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional Activities, 1958-1983; 4
  - Advances in Immunology, 4.1
    - "Immunologic Regulation of Fetal-Material Balance," by David R. Jacoby, Lars B. Olding and Michael B.A. Oldstone - Vol.35, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - "The Influence of Histamine on Immune and Inflammatory Responses," by Dennis J. Beer, Steven M. Matloffand Ross E. Rocklin, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - "Interferons with Special Emphasis on the Immune System," by Robert M. Freidman and Stefanie Vogel, 29-Apr-82 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - "Interferons with Special Emphasis on the Immune System," by Robert M. Freidman and Stefanie Vogel - Vol. 34, 1982 October (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - "Lectin Receptors as Lymphocyte Surface Markers," by Nathan Sharon-Review, 1982 April (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Letter - Thomas A. Waldmann, 1981 August 3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - "Major Role of Macrophage in Quantitative Genetic Regulation of Immunoresponsiveness and Anti-Infectious Immunity," by Guido Biozzi, 1983 November (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - "The Murine Antitumor Immune Response and its Therapeutic Manipulation," by Robert J. North, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Robert J. North, 1983 January 21 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Ted H. Hanset, et al. "Heterogeneity of H-2D Region Associated Genes and Gene Products", 1983 January (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Vol. XI, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Vol. X, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 12 & 13, 1967-1971 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 14-16, 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 23, 1972-1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Workshops and Symposia, 4.2
    - Advance Programme - 5th SEAPAL Congress of Rheumatology- Bangkok, Thailand, 1984 January 22-27 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Advances in Immunology Symposium in Honor of Dr. Elvin A. Kabat's 65th Birthday - Columbia University, 1979 October 17 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - The American Academy of Allergy - "Allergy and Immunology for the Clinician" - Hilton Head Island- 1981 October 30-31/ 38th Annual Meeting - Montreal, Quebec, 1982 March 6-10, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - The American Academy of Allergy - News & Notes and Information - 38th Annual Meeting - Montreal, 1982 March 6-10 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - The American Academy of Allergy - 38th Annual Meeting - Rules for Abstracts - Montreal, Quebec, 1982 March 6-10 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - The American Academy of Allergy & Immunology - News & Notes and Information - 39th Annual Meeting - Hollywood, FL, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - American Federation for Clinical Research - Annual Eastern Section Meeting ? Information - Boston, 1981 October 23-24 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - American Federation for Clinical Research - Regional & National Meetings ? Information, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - American Federation for Clinical Research - Information & Call for Abstracts - Regional & National Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - American Rheumatism Association - Abstract Reproduction Forms, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - American Rheumatism Association - Northeastern Regional Meeting - Program & Notes - New York, 1980 November 12-14 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - American Rheumatism Association - Abstract Reproduction Forms, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - American Rheumatism Association - Annual Scientific Meeting?Program - 16th Annual Meeting of the Arthritis Health Professions Association - Boston, 1981 June 3-6 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - American Rheumatism Association - ARA National Annual Scientific Meeting - Registration Infonnation - Boston, 1981 June 3-6 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - American Rheumatism Association - ARA Northeastern Regional Meeting- Call for Abstracts & Information - Montreal, Quebec, 1981 October 22-23 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - American Rheumatism Association - ARA Northeastern Regional Meeting ? Information - Montreal, Quebec, 1981 October 22-23 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - American Rheumatism Association - Eighth Northeastern Regional Meeting ? Arthritis Health Professions Association - Sixth Northeastern Regional Meeting - Montreal, Quebec, 1981 October 22-23 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - American Rheumatism Association, section of the Arthritis Foundation ? Information - ARA Annual Meeting and VIII Pan-American Congress of Rheumatology, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - American Society of Biological Chemists- General Information for ASBC Members, 1980 September (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - American Society of Biological Chemists - 72nd Annual Meeting?Information - St. Louis, 1981 May/June (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - American Society for Clinical Investigation - 73rd Annual Meeting ? Nominations for Membership & Minutes- Washington, D.C., 1981 February 24-26 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - American Society for Clinical Investigation- Information- 74th Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C, 1982 May 7 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Announcements - 39th Annual Congress - American College of Allergists ? New Orleans, LA, 1983 January-February (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Arden House, P & S Biomedical Sciences Symposia, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Arthritis Foundation - 15th International Congress of Rheumatology - Program & Information - Paris, France, 1981 June 21-27 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - The Arthritis Foundation - 5th Annual Winter Rheumatology Symposium ? Program - Snowmass, CO, 1982 January 17-22 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Association of American Physicians - 94th Annual Meeting - Program & Invitation - San Francisco, CA, 1981 April 25-27 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Association of American Physicians/American Society for Clinical Investigation/American Federation for Clinical Research - Annual Meeting - Infonnation - San Francisco, 1981 April 25-27 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - The Association of American Physicians - Program - 95th Annual Meeting ? Washington, D.C., 1982 May 7-10 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Association of American Physicians - 95th Meeting- Washington, D.C., 1982 May 7-10 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Baltimore, 1981 June (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Basel Institute for Immunology - Symposium to Celebrate the Tenth Anniversary of the Basel Institute for Immunology- "The Immune System" - Basel, Switzerland, 1981 June 16-17 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Bona Meeting- National Academy of Sciences-International Conference on Immune Networks, 1982 November 29-December 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Buffalo, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Call for Abstracts - Regional & National Meetings, 1983-1984 - Clinical Research, official publication of the American Federation for Clinical Research (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - The Canadian Society for Immunology - International Symposium on the Structure and Function of Fe Receptors - First Circular - Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1981 June 1-3 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Center for Blood Research - Fourth International Workshop for the Genetics of the Complement System - Boston, 1982 July 13-15 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Columbia University, College of Physicians & Surgeons - P &S Biomedical Sciences Symposia: Pathology of the Endothelial Cell- Program ? Columbia University, 1981 June 5-7 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Itinerary - 5th Congress of lmmunology - Kyoto, Japan, 1983 August 21-27 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - European League Against Rheumatism - Second European Workshop on Rheumatology Research - Leiden, Holland, 1982 February 18-19 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology - 65th Annual Meeting - Information- Atlanta, GA, 1981 April 12-17 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Florida - Hughes, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Fourth International Congress of lmmunology - Paris, 1980 July 21-26 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Hughes- Florida, 1982 March 21-23, 1981-1983 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Hughes - Florida, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Human B Cell Workshop - Program, Notes & Notebook - Washington, D.C., 1980 September 17-20 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - ICP International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology, 1980-1983 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Idiotype Meeting, 1981 July 13-17 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Immunopathology Symposium - Paper, SLE and Discussion, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Information - Annual Eastern Section Meeting - American Federation for Clinical Research - Cambridge, MA, 1983 October 14-15 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Information - Annual Meeting - The National Academy of Sciences, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Information & Call for Abstracts - Ninth ARA Northeastern Regional Meeting - Northeastern Region, American Rheumatism Association Section of the Arthritis Foundation - Boston, 1982 October 28-29 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Information & Call for Abstracts - Tenth ARA Northeastern Regional Meeting - Northeastern Region, American Rheumatism Association Section of the Arthritis Foundation- Providence, RI, 1983 November 16-18 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Information- Immunoglobulins: Genes, Receptors, Therapy - Center for Blood Research - Boston, 1983 April 4-5 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Information & Minutes - 74th Annual Meeting - American Society for Clinical Investigation - Park City, UT, 1982 February 17-20 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Information - 74th Annual Meeting - American Society of Biological Chemists - San Francisco, CA, 1983 June 5-9 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Inserm Conferences - B-Cell Differentiation and Idiotypes - Program, 1979 October 1-4 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - International Congress of Allergology & Clinical Immunology-XI - Program & Information - London, 1982 October 17-22 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - International Immunopathology Symposium-VIII - October 1980, 1980 October (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - The International Scientific Committee - Program, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - International Union ofimmunological Societies (WIS) - 5th International Congress of Immunology - First Announcement - Kyoto, Japan, 1983 August 21-27 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - The Interurban Clinical Club - Program - Meeting - Philadelphia, 1981 December 4-5 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Interurban Clinical Club - 145th Meeting, 1982 April 2-3 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Invitation - Annual Meeting Dinner Lecture Reception - The New York Academy of Sciences - NYC, 1983 December 7 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Italian National Institute for the Care of the Aged (INRCA) - International Workshop, "Immunoregulation 1981" - Urbino, Italy, 1981 July 8-10 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - The Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, The Dept. of Pharmacology & Experimental Therapeutics - John Jacob Abel Symposium on Drug Development. "Monoclonal Antibodies in Drug Development"- Baltimore, MD, 1981 June 8-10 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - La Jolla Sununer Conference on Allergy, Immunology and Rheumatology ? Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation -1983 Updates - La Jolla, CA, 1983 August 5-7 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - McDavitt, undated (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Minutes of the 1983 Council Meeting - Seventy-Fourth Annual Meeting ? American Society for Clinical Investigation - Sarasota, FL, 1983 February 22-25 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Misc. Conference Notes, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - National Academy of Sciences - 118th Annual Meeting - Program & Information - Washington, D.C., 1981 April 26-29 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Sciences- Preliminary Program- 119th Annual Meeting ? Washington, D.C., 1982 April 25-28 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - National Academy of Sciences - 120th Annual Meeting - Program ? Washington, D.C., 1983 April 24-27 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences - Conference on C-Reactive Protein and the Plasma Protein Response to Tissue Injury - Program - New York City, 1981 September 21-23 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences - Conference on Immunological Tolerance to Self and Non-Self- Program - New York City, 1981 October 19-21 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - NY Academy of Sciences - Conference on the Secretory Immune System, 1982 May 4-7 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Notice - ARA 1983 Annual Business Meeting - American Rheumatism Association, a section of the Arthritis Foundation (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Pan-American Congress on Rheumatic Diseases - VI - Program - Toronto, 1974 June 16-21 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Pan-American Congress of Rheumatology, VIII - Washington, D.C., 1982 June 7- 12, 1982 March-June (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Pan-American Congress of Rheumatology, VIII - Program - Washington, D.C., 1982 June 7-12 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Pan-American League Against Rheumatism & the Arthritis Foundation - VIII Pan-American Congress of Rheumatology - Information - Washington, D.C., 1982 June 7-12 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Phoenix Conf. on B Cells, 1978 October (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Preliminary announcement - Third International Paul Ehrlich Seminar on Regulatory Control and Standardization of Allergenic Extracts - Paul Ehrlich Institute - Louvain, Belgium, 1982 December (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Program - 18th Interim Scientific Session of the American Rheumatism Association Section of the Arthritis Foundation - Pittsburgh, 1972 December 7-9 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Program - Eighty-Seventh Annual Meeting of the Association of American Physicians - Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1974 May 7 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Program - First International Conference - "Therapeutic Control of Inflammatory Diseases"- Inflammation Research Association - Liberty, New York, 1982 November 14-17 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & S Biomedical Sciences Symposia - Cells of Immunoglobulin Synthesis? Arden House, Columbia University, 1978 June 9-11 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Registration Information - Tenth ARA Northeastern Regional Meeting? Northeastern Region, American Rheumatism Association Section of the Arthritis Foundation - Providence, RI, 1983 November 16-18 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Report - American Rheumatism Foundation - Committee for Evaluation of Research on Rheumatic Diseases, 1972 May (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Rules Applying to Abstracts - 39th Annual Meeting - The American Academy of Allergy & Immunology - Hollywood, Florida, 1983 March 19-23 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Schedule & Forms - Seventy-Fifth Annual Meeting - American Society for Clinical Investigation - Washington, D.C., 1983 April/May (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Schedule - Ninety-Sixth Annual Meeting - Association of American Physicians - Washington, D.C., 1983 April/May (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Second International Symposium on Immunobiology of Proteins - Program & Information - Tahoe City, CA, 1981 September 8-11 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Seminar, Rockefeller University - Prof. Sarah Fuchs, Weizmann Institute of Science, 1983 October 31 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Shelter Island, undated (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Simposio Interamericano de Inflamacion - Program - Bogota, Colombia, 1979 October 31-November 2 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - SLE Symposium - Philadelphia, 1981 June 7-9 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Sloan Kettering, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Symposium program - "Thymic Hormones and Lymphokines," - George Washington University Spring Symposium on Health Sciences ? Washington, D.C., 1983 May/June (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Symposium sponsored by the American Cancer Society - "Conference on Tumor -Specific Antigens" - Program & Papers - Westchester Country Club ? Rye, NY, 1967 November 13-15 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Talk of Dr. from Roswell Park Cancer Institute, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 3rd International Paul Ehrlich Seminar on Regulatory Control and Standardization of Allergenic Extracts - Paul Ehrlich Institute - Louvain, Belgium, 1983 September 18-21 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Transcription of the proceedings of a workshop held at Rockefeller Institute, 1972 May 12 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - The Transplantation Society - Program & Information - Third International Immunological Monitoring Symposium - Key Biscayne, FL, 1982 November 21-24 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - University of Alberta, Department of lmmunology - International Conference on Reproductive Immunology - Program - Banff, Alberta, Canada, 1981 May 15-18 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - University of Miami, Dept of Biochemistry - 14th Miami Winter Symposium ? From Gene to Protein: Translation into Biotecimology" - Miami, FL, 1982 January 11-15 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Untitled Conference, January 17-19 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Untitled Conference Notes, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Journal of Experimental Medicine, 4.3
    - Activation of T Lymphocytes by Lectins and Carbohydrate Oxidizing Reagents. Viewed as an Immunological Recognition of Cell - Surface Modifications Seen in the Context of "Self" Major Histocompatability Complex Antigens" - Arthur Kimura and Bo Ersson, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Anderson, Kenneth C. - "Expression of Human B Cell Associated Antigens on Leukemias and Lymphomas", 1983 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Amaout, M. Amin - "Deficiency of LFA-1, a Surface Glycoprotein Associated with Lymphocyte Functions in a Patient with Mol Deficiency Structural and Functional Studies", undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Beaulieu, Andre D. - "The Role of Fibronectin in the Cryoprecipitation of Monoclonal Cryoglobulins", 1982 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Birnbaum, G. - "Spinal Fluid Lymphocytes Responsive to Autologous and Allogenic Cells in Multiple Sclerosis and Control Individuals", 1984 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Blaese, R. Michael - "Suppressor T Cell Function in Man", undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Chanh, Tran C. - "T Cell Hybrids That Express a VH Idiotype -Related Determinant on a Glycoprotein Distinct from H-2, THY-1 and LYT-1 Molecules", undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Choi, Yong Sung - "Human B-Cell Differentiation in the Absence of Pokeweed Mitogen" (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Damle, Nitin K. - "Autologous Mixed Lymphocyte Reaction in Man", 1981 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - De Kruyff, Rosemarie H. - "Hapten Reactive Inducer T Cells. II. Evidence that a Secreted Form of the T cell receptor induces antibody production", 1983 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Doherty, Peter - "Inhibition of Autoimmune Neuropathological Process by Treatment with an Iron Chelating Agent", 1983 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Fauci, Anthony S. - "Activation and Immunoregulation of Antigen -Specific Human B Lymphocyte Responses. Multifaceted Role of the Monocyte", 1981 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Glimcher, Laurie H. - "Production of Autoreactive I - Region Restricted T Cell Hybridomas", 1982 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Grimm, Elizabeth A. - "The Lymphokine Activated Killer Cell Phenomenon", 1982 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Hansson, Mona - "Epstein -Barr virus transformation of human pre-B cells"?, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Howard, Maureen - "Identification of a T-Cell Derived B-Cell Growth Factor Distinct from Interleukin 2", undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Howard, Maureen - "Role of lnterleukin 1 in Anti-Immunoglobulin-Induced B Cell Proliferation", undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - "Immunoglobulin Expression by Human B-Lymphocytes Clonally Transformed by Epstein-Barr Virus" - George Miller and Nathaniel Brown, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - The In Vitro Primary Immune Response of Mouse Spleen Cells in the Absence of Exogenous Proteins" - Mikulas Burger (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Kehrl, John H. - "Identification, Purification, and Characterization of Antigen?Activated and Antigen-Specific Human B Lymphocytes", 1982 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Knaab, S. and M. Jeannel - "A Simplified Technique for the Evaluation of Suppressor Cell Activity in Man", 1981 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Kristensen, Tom - "A Cloned Human T Lymphocyte Suppressing Polyclonal B Lymphocyte Proliferation In Vitro with Exquisite Genetic Restriction", undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Lane, H. Clifford - "Human Monoclonal Anti-KLH Antibody - Secreting Hybridoma Produced from Peripheral Blood B Lymphocytes of a KLH Immune Individual", 1981 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Lehner, Thomas - "Separation and characterization of a subset of human T8+ cells which function as antigen binding, presenting and contra -suppressor cells", undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Litvin, David A. -"Characterization of Warm -Reactive IgG Anti -Lymphocyte Antibodies in Systemic Lupus Erythmatosus SLE", undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Masuda, T. - "Suppresive B cell factor (SBF), produced by FcR-y bearing B cells; the growth inhibition of B, but not non B cells", 1982 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Miller, R.G. - "A Glycopeptide Extract Can Inhibit Cytotoxic T Lymphocyte?target Cell Conjugation in an H-2 Restricted Manner", 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Mongini, Patricia K.A. -"IgG Subclass, IgE, and IgA Anti-TNP Antibody Production Within TNP-Ficoll Responsive B Cell Clones", undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - "The Murine Syngenic Mixed Lymphocyte Response. L The Target Antigens Are Selfia Molecules" - Laurie H. Glimcher et al., undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Nemazee, David A. - "Induction of Enhancing Antibodies in the Mouse-Regulated Production of Rheumatoid Antibody in the Second Humoral Response", undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - North, Robert J. - "Cyclophosphamide -Facilitated Adoptive Immunotherapy of an Established Tumor Depends on Elimination of Tumor-Induced Suppressor T Cells", undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Okada, Jun - "Alloantigens Expressed on a Subset of Unstimulated Human T Lymphocytes with Suppressor Function", undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Okada, Masaji - "B Cell Growth Factors (BCGF) and B Cell Differentiation Factor (BCDF) From Human T Hybridomas", undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Okudaira, Kunio - "Anti-IA Antibody in the Sera ofNonnal Subjects After In Vivo Antigenic Stimulation", 1981 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Polyclonal Activators of Human Peripheral Blood B Lymphocytes in the Study of Cellular Interactions Controlling Immunoglobulin Synthesis" ? Thomas A. Waldmaun et al., 1980 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Puck, Jennifer M. and Robert Rich - "Regulatory Interactions Governing the Proliferation of T Cell Subsets Stimulated with Pokeweed Mitogen", undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Rheum. Factors Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Schultheib, Heinz-Peter - "Inhibition of the Adenine Nucleotide Translocator by Organ Specific Auto-Antibodies in Primary Bilary Cirrhosis", undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Serban, Dan - "The Participation of Trimethylammonium in the Mouse Erythrocyte Epitope Recognized by Monoclonal Auto-antibodies", 1981 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Soltis, Ronald D. - "I. C1 Q Binding Activity During Acute Serum Sickness in the Rabbit. II. Detection of Insoluble Complexes in Whole Blood and Plasma", undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Steinman, Ralph M. - "Dendritic Cells are the Principal Stimulators of the Primary Mixed Leukocyte Reaction in Mice", undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Untitled Loose Manuscript Pages, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Wang, Chang Yi - "Human T8 Antigen, Structural Homology to the Murine LYT-2 Antigen", 1983 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Lectures and Manuscripts, 4.4
    - Lecture: American Association of Immunology (on ethics), undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Lecture: Bona, Idiotypy - RU and Untitled, 1977-1983 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Lecture: Grad. Talks - Alice, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Lecture: Harvey Society Presentation - Muller-Eberhard, Scharff & Lawrence, 1967-1978 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Lecture: Hoffman-La Roche Lectures - Rutgers - Piscataway, NJ, 1980 October 2-3, 1963, 1970, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Lecture: Idiotypes talk, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Lecture: Idiotypes Talk to Lab, April 30 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Lecture: INSERM - immunodeficiencies - Royaumont (Paris), 1980 July 17-20 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Lecture: Miami, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Lecture: Nobel Academy, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)